{"case_id":"207348ac7787458ebb8986947d713ce6","generated_at":"2025-11-27T18:41:41.653478","timeline_events":1,"inconsistencies":0,"missing_evidence":["Check for forensic reports (fingerprints, DNA analysis, blood spatter analysis).","No witness statements found. Consider obtaining statements from witnesses and bystanders.","No CCTV footage or surveillance images found. Consider collecting CCTV from nearby locations.","Collect phone records and call logs if applicable.","Limited time coverage. Consider collecting evidence from extended time periods before and after the incident.","Verify alibis and cross-check with CCTV timestamps.","Obtain statements from neighbors and nearby residents.","No medical reports found. If injuries occurred, obtain medical examination reports."],"report_path":"storage\\reports\\207348ac7787458ebb8986947d713ce6.pdf","preview":{"timeline":["STARTUP PILOT – GUIDING TEAMS\nFROM CHAOS TO CLARITY\nProject report submitted to Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management,\nNagpur in partial fulfillment of requirement for the award of\ndegree of\nHONORS\nIn\nCOMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nBy\nVedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\nAnshdeep Singh Bhandari – Computer Science\nand Engineering\nGuide\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat\nDEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nShri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management, Nagpur\n440..."],"inconsistencies":[],"extracted_content":[{"file_type":"document","classification":{"label":"fir","confidence":0.7658690512180328,"method":"BERT"},"extracted_text":"STARTUP PILOT – GUIDING TEAMS\nFROM CHAOS TO CLARITY\nProject report submitted to Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management,\nNagpur in partial fulfillment of requirement for the award of\ndegree of\nHONORS\nIn\nCOMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nBy\nVedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\nAnshdeep Singh Bhandari – Computer Science\nand Engineering\nGuide\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat\nDEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nShri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management, Nagpur\n440013\n(An Autonomous Institute affiliated to Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University Nagpur)\n2025 - 2026\nSTARTUP PILOT – GUIDING TEAMS\nFROM CHAOS TO CLARITY\nProject report submitted to Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management,\nNagpur in partial fulfillment of requirement for the award of\ndegree of\nHONORS\nIn\nCOMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nBy\nVedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\nAnshdeep Singh Bhandari – Computer Science\nand Engineering\nGuide\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat\nDEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nShri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management, Nagpur\n440013\n(An Autonomous Institute affiliated to Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University Nagpur)\n2025 - 2026\nSHRI RAMDEOBABA COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING & MANAGEMENT,\nNAGPUR\n(An Autonomous Institute Affiliated to Rashtrasant Tukdoji Maharaj Nagpur University\nNagpur)\nCOMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nThis is to certify that the Thesis on “Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams from Chaos to\nClarity is a bonafide work of Vedika Jaipurkar, Anshdeep Singh Bhandari of Computer\nScience and Engineering submitted to the Rashtrasant Tukdoji Maharaj Nagpur\nUniversity, Nagpur in partial fulfillment of the award of a Honors has been carried out at\nComputer Science and Engineering, Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering and\nManagement, Nagpur during the academic year 2025-2026.\n_________________ ________________\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat Dr. Preeti Voditel\nProject Guide H.O.D\nDepartment of Computer Department of Computer\nScience and Engineering Science and Engineering\n________________\nDr. M. B. Chandak\nPrincipal\nDECLARATION\nWe hereby declare that the project report titled “Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams from\nChaos to Clarity” submitted herein, has been carried out in the Department of\nComputer Science and Engineering of Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering and\nManagement, Nagpur. The work is original and has not been submitted earlier as a\nwhole or part for the award of any degree/diploma at this or any other institution /\nUniversity.\nDate:\nPlace: Nagpur\nName of the Student Department Signature\nVedika Jaipurkar Computer Science and Engineering\nAnshdeep Singh Bhandari Computer Science and Engineering\nAPPROVAL SHEET\nThis report entitled Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams from Chaos to Clarity\nby Vedika Jaipurkar, Anshdeep Singh Bhandari from department of Computer\nScience and Engineering is approved for the degree of Honors in Computer\nScience and Engineering.\n______________ ________________\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat External Examiner\nProject Guide\nDepartment of Computer\nScience and Engineering\n_______________\nDr. Preeti Voditel\nHead of Department\nDepartment of Computer\nScience and Engineering\nDate:\nPlace: Nagpur\nACKNOWLEDGEMENT\nThe project is a combined effort of a group of individuals who synergize to contribute\ntowards the desired objectives. Apart from the efforts by us, the success of the project\nshares an equal proportion on the engagement and guidance of many others. We take this\nopportunity to express our gratitude to the people who have been instrumental in the\nsuccessful completion of this project.\nWe would like to extend our heartfelt thanks to Prof. Vishwas Bhagwat for his support\nand encouragement during this project. His knowledge, expertise, and willingness to\nhelp have been instrumental in the successful completion of this work.\nWe would like to show our greatest appreciation towards Dr. Preeti Voditel, Head,\nDepartment of Computer Science and Engineering, RCOEM, Nagpur for providing us\nwith the facilities for completing this project and for his constant guidance.\nWe would like to express our deepest gratitude to Dr. M.B. Chandak, Principal, RCOEM,\nNagpur for providing us the opportunity to embark on this project.\nFinally, we extend our gratitude to all the faculty members of the CSE department who\nhave always been so supportive and provided the resources needed in our project\ndevelopment. We are very grateful to all of them who have unconditionally supported us\nthroughout the project.\nDate: - Projectees\ni\nABSTRACT\nStartup Pilot is a unified digital platform designed to support early-stage startups by\nproviding structured workflow management, investor connectivity, and intelligent guidance\nthrough an integrated web-based system. Startups often struggle with unorganized task\ndistribution, unclear team roles, and fragmented communication, leading to inefficiencies,\nmissed deadlines, and challenges in strategic planning. The proposed system addre","entities":[{"entity":"CHAOS TO","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":35,"end":43},{"entity":"Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management","label":"ORG","start":80,"end":131},{"entity":"Nagpur","label":"ORG","start":133,"end":139},{"entity":"Vedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\n","label":"PERSON","start":251,"end":303},{"entity":"Anshdeep Singh Bhandari","label":"PERSON","start":303,"end":326},{"entity":"Guide","label":"GPE","start":362,"end":367},{"entity":"Vishwas Bhagwat","label":"PERSON","start":374,"end":389},{"entity":"Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management","label":"ORG","start":437,"end":488},{"entity":"440013","label":"DATE","start":497,"end":503},{"entity":"An Autonomous Institute","label":"ORG","start":505,"end":528},{"entity":"Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University Nagpur","label":"PERSON","start":543,"end":596},{"entity":"2025 - 2026","label":"DATE","start":598,"end":609},{"entity":"CHAOS TO","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":645,"end":653},{"entity":"Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management","label":"ORG","start":690,"end":741},{"entity":"Nagpur","label":"ORG","start":743,"end":749},{"entity":"Vedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\n","label":"PERSON","start":861,"end":913},{"entity":"Anshdeep Singh Bhandari","label":"PERSON","start":913,"end":936},{"entity":"Guide","label":"GPE","start":972,"end":977},{"entity":"Vishwas Bhagwat","label":"PERSON","start":984,"end":999},{"entity":"Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management","label":"ORG","start":1047,"end":1098},{"entity":"440013","label":"DATE","start":1107,"end":1113},{"entity":"An Autonomous Institute","label":"ORG","start":1115,"end":1138},{"entity":"Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University Nagpur","label":"PERSON","start":1153,"end":1206},{"entity":"2025 - 2026","label":"DATE","start":1208,"end":1219},{"entity":"NAGPUR","label":"ORG","start":1273,"end":1279},{"entity":"An Autonomous Institute Affiliated","label":"ORG","start":1281,"end":1315},{"entity":"Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":1445,"end":1474},{"entity":"Chaos","label":"GPE","start":1480,"end":1485},{"entity":"Vedika Jaipurkar","label":"PERSON","start":1519,"end":1535},{"entity":"Anshdeep Singh Bhandari","label":"PERSON","start":1537,"end":1560},{"entity":"Computer\nScience and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":1564,"end":1596},{"entity":"Honors","label":"ORG","start":1709,"end":1715},{"entity":"Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering","label":"ORG","start":1774,"end":1812},{"entity":"the academic year 2025-2026","label":"DATE","start":1843,"end":1870},{"entity":"Vishwas Bhagwat","label":"PERSON","start":1913,"end":1928},{"entity":"Preeti Voditel","label":"PERSON","start":1933,"end":1947},{"entity":"Project Guide","label":"ORG","start":1948,"end":1961},{"entity":"H.O.D\nDepartment of Computer Department of Computer\nScience and Engineering Science and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":1962,"end":2061},{"entity":"M. B. Chandak","label":"PERSON","start":2083,"end":2096},{"entity":"Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":2169,"end":2198},{"entity":"Chaos to Clarity","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":2204,"end":2220},{"entity":"the Department of\nComputer Science and Engineering of Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering","label":"ORG","start":2264,"end":2356},{"entity":"the Student Department Signature\nVedika Jaipurkar Computer Science and Engineering\n","label":"ORG","start":2567,"end":2650},{"entity":"Anshdeep Singh Bhandari Computer","label":"PERSON","start":2650,"end":2682},{"entity":"Startup Pilot – Guiding Teams","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":2743,"end":2772},{"entity":"Chaos","label":"GPE","start":2778,"end":2783},{"entity":"Vedika Jaipurkar","label":"PERSON","start":2798,"end":2814},{"entity":"Anshdeep Singh Bhandari","label":"PERSON","start":2816,"end":2839},{"entity":"Computer\nScience and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":2859,"end":2891},{"entity":"Computer\nScience and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":2932,"end":2964},{"entity":"Vishwas Bhagwat External Examiner","label":"PERSON","start":3004,"end":3037},{"entity":"Project Guide\nDepartment of Computer\nScience and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":3038,"end":3098},{"entity":"Preeti Voditel","label":"PERSON","start":3119,"end":3133},{"entity":"Department\nDepartment of Computer\nScience and Engineering\nDate","label":"ORG","start":3142,"end":3204},{"entity":"Vishwas Bhagwat","label":"PERSON","start":3677,"end":3692},{"entity":"Preeti Voditel","label":"PERSON","start":3924,"end":3938},{"entity":"Department of Computer Science and Engineering","label":"ORG","start":3946,"end":3992},{"entity":"Nagpur","label":"PERSON","start":4001,"end":4007},{"entity":"M.B. Chandak","label":"PERSON","start":4158,"end":4170},{"entity":"Principal","label":"PERSON","start":4172,"end":4181},{"entity":"RCOEM","label":"ORG","start":4183,"end":4188},{"entity":"Nagpur","label":"ORG","start":4190,"end":4196},{"entity":"CSE","label":"ORG","start":4324,"end":4327},{"entity":"three","label":"CARDINAL","start":5231,"end":5236},{"entity":"Project & Task Management System","label":"ORG","start":5254,"end":5286},{"entity":"Retrieval-Augmented\nGeneration","label":"ORG","start":5539,"end":5569},{"entity":"Built using React","label":"ORG","start":5646,"end":5663},{"entity":"CI","label":"PERSON","start":5694,"end":5696},{"entity":"AI","label":"ORG","start":6199,"end":6201},{"entity":"Startup Pilot","label":"PERSON","start":6259,"end":6272},{"entity":"Acknowledgment","label":"GPE","start":6613,"end":6627},{"entity":"List of Figures","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":6642,"end":6657},{"entity":"List of Tables v\nList of Abbreviations","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":6661,"end":6699},{"entity":"CHAPTER 1","label":"LAW","start":6703,"end":6712},{"entity":"1 - 3","label":"CARDINAL","start":6727,"end":6732},{"entity":"1.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":6733,"end":6736},{"entity":"1","label":"CARDINAL","start":6756,"end":6757},{"entity":"1","label":"CARDINAL","start":6781,"end":6782},{"entity":"1.3","label":"CARDINAL","start":6783,"end":6786},{"entity":"Objectives","label":"ORG","start":6787,"end":6797},{"entity":"1 - 2","label":"PRODUCT","start":6798,"end":6803},{"entity":"1.4","label":"CARDINAL","start":6804,"end":6807},{"entity":"2","label":"CARDINAL","start":6821,"end":6822},{"entity":"1.5","label":"CARDINAL","start":6823,"end":6826},{"entity":"Block","label":"ORG","start":6827,"end":6832},{"entity":"4","label":"CARDINAL","start":6880,"end":6881},{"entity":"2.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":6887,"end":6890},{"entity":"4 - 10","label":"CARDINAL","start":6909,"end":6915},{"entity":"2.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":6916,"end":6919},{"entity":"10 - 11","label":"CARDINAL","start":6947,"end":6954},{"entity":"Motivation","label":"ORG","start":6959,"end":6969},{"entity":"2.4","label":"CARDINAL","start":6978,"end":6981},{"entity":"Technical Specifications","label":"ORG","start":6982,"end":7006},{"entity":"13","label":"CARDINAL","start":7007,"end":7009},{"entity":"CHAPTER 3","label":"LAW","start":7015,"end":7024},{"entity":"15","label":"CARDINAL","start":7038,"end":7040},{"entity":"3.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":7046,"end":7049},{"entity":"15","label":"CARDINAL","start":7066,"end":7068},{"entity":"3.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":7069,"end":7072},{"entity":"16 - 17","label":"CARDINAL","start":7090,"end":7097},{"entity":"3.3","label":"CARDINAL","start":7098,"end":7101},{"entity":"17 - 21","label":"CARDINAL","start":7126,"end":7133},{"entity":"3.4","label":"CARDINAL","start":7134,"end":7137},{"entity":"21","label":"CARDINAL","start":7162,"end":7164},{"entity":"CHAPTER 4","label":"LAW","start":7214,"end":7223},{"entity":"24","label":"CARDINAL","start":7248,"end":7250},{"entity":"4.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":7251,"end":7254},{"entity":"24 - 28","label":"CARDINAL","start":7276,"end":7283},{"entity":"4.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":7284,"end":7287},{"entity":"28 - 29","label":"CARDINAL","start":7310,"end":7317},{"entity":"CHAPTER 5","label":"LAW","start":7318,"end":7327},{"entity":"30","label":"CARDINAL","start":7340,"end":7342},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7368,"end":7371},{"entity":"Caption Page","label":"PERSON","start":7383,"end":7395},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7400,"end":7403},{"entity":"1.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":7405,"end":7408},{"entity":"3.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":7430,"end":7433},{"entity":"Startup Pilot","label":"PERSON","start":7434,"end":7447},{"entity":"7","label":"CARDINAL","start":7474,"end":7475},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7476,"end":7479},{"entity":"3.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":7481,"end":7484},{"entity":"8","label":"CARDINAL","start":7525,"end":7526},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7527,"end":7530},{"entity":"4.1","label":"CARDINAL","start":7532,"end":7535},{"entity":"Dashboard","label":"PERSON","start":7536,"end":7545},{"entity":"Startups","label":"PRODUCT","start":7565,"end":7573},{"entity":"10\nFig","label":"PRODUCT","start":7574,"end":7580},{"entity":"4.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":7582,"end":7585},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7603,"end":7606},{"entity":"4.3","label":"CARDINAL","start":7608,"end":7611},{"entity":"Page 11","label":"DATE","start":7618,"end":7625},{"entity":"Fig","label":"PERSON","start":7626,"end":7629},{"entity":"4.4","label":"CARDINAL","start":7631,"end":7634},{"entity":"13","label":"CARDINAL","start":7650,"end":7652},{"entity":"CHAPTER 1","label":"LAW","start":7656,"end":7665},{"entity":"1.1 Problem Definition","label":"MONEY","start":7679,"end":7701},{"entity":"1.2","label":"CARDINAL","start":8128,"end":8131},{"entity":"Startup Pilot","label":"PERSON","start":8508,"end":8521},{"entity":"Startup Pilot","label":"ORG","start":8670,"end":8683},{"entity":"AI","label":"ORG","start":8769,"end":8771},{"entity":"AI","label":"ORG","start":8871,"end":8873},{"entity":"1.3","label":"CARDINAL","start":9248,"end":9251},{"entity":"Objectives","label":"ORG","start":9252,"end":9262},{"entity":"1","label":"CARDINAL","start":9263,"end":9264},{"entity":"2","label":"CARDINAL","start":9369,"end":9370},{"entity":"3","label":"CARDINAL","start":9449,"end":9450},{"entity":"1","label":"CARDINAL","start":9538,"end":9539},{"entity":"5","label":"CARDINAL","start":9631,"end":9632},{"entity":"6","label":"CARDINAL","start":9721,"end":9722},{"entity":"Startups","label":"PRODUCT","start":9789,"end":9797},{"entity":"1.4 Applications\n▪ Entrepreneurship Guidance: Helps","label":"WORK_OF_ART","start":9911,"end":9962}],"objects_detected":[],"ocr_text":"","timestamps":[],"locations":[],"summary":"STARTUP PILOT – GUIDING TEAMS\nFROM CHAOS TO CLARITY\nProject report submitted to Shri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management,\nNagpur in partial fulfillment of requirement for the award of\ndegree of\nHONORS\nIn\nCOMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nBy\nVedika Jaipurkar - Computer Science and Engineering\nAnshdeep Singh Bhandari – Computer Science\nand Engineering\nGuide\nProf. Vishwas Bhagwat\nDEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING\nShri Ramdeobaba College of Engineering & Management, Nagpur\n440...","dates":[],"events":[{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"m Overview 15\n3.2 Proposed Modules 16 - 17\n3.3 Architectural Framework 17 - 21\n3.4 Methodological Workf"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":". 1.1 Block Diagram 5\nFig. 3.1 Startup Pilot - Architectural framework 7\nFig. 3.2 Startup Pilot – Metho"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"Authentication: JWT-based authentication\n• API Architecture: REST APIs\nDatabase\n• DB Type: NoSQL\n• Data"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":" (Frontend), Render / Railway (Backend)\nSystem Architecture\n• Component-based frontend architecture\n• M"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"System Architecture\n• Component-based frontend architecture\n• Modular backend with route-based API stru"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"em using RAG all supported by a strong backend\narchitecture, CI/CD pipeline, and Git-based version cont"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":".\nThis chapter details the methodology, system architecture, workflow, algorithms, and\ndesign rationale"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"data\nTo solve these, the system uses a modular architecture consisting of:\n• User Management & Authenti"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"APIs and follows a scalable microservice-ready\narchitecture.\n15\n3.2 Proposed Modules\n3.2.1 Module 1: Pr"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"suggestions\n• Scalable knowledge retrieval\n3.3 Architectural Framework\nThe methodology adopted for this"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"n of this workflow.\n17\nFig 3.1 Startup Pilot – Architectural Framework\nThe flowchart clearly illustrate"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"\n• Scales easily due to modular and API-driven architecture\n• Enables professional software engineering"},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"nal design has been integrated into the system architecture to enable\nfuture expansion. The planned AI "},{"event":"hit","type":"violence","context":"enhances readability, while\nstrategically placed whitespace improves focus and reduces visual fatigue. "}]}]}}